Guide to the Ralph E. Griswold Collection, GWSM, Inc., 1912-1988 AIS.2001.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Project Files, 1917-1976; V.
  - Garden Club of Virginia Material, undated; 4.
    The Garden Club of Virginia is an active association of garden clubs responsible for many of Virginia's historic garden restoration including Monticello. Griswold was a part of the Garden Club of Virginia Restoration Committee, and this subseries documents his relationship with committee members and relates to several club projects. The Garden Club of Virginia, much like Griswold himself, was interested in historic preservation. The garden clubs restoration projects began in 1927, however, Griswold was not involved until the late 1950s. The restoration effort in which Griswold was involved included the Mary Washington House, Colonial Williamsburg, Monticello, Kent Valentine House, Woodrow Wilson House, Scotchtown, St. Johns Mews, Agecroft Hall, Morgan Mill, University of Virginia, and Christ Church of Middlesex County. Griswold was either the main landscape architect or landscape consultant on these restoration projects. He was also responsible for revitalization projects related to a chapel at Washington College in Lexington, Virginia, that had been built during Robert E. Lee's tenure as university president.
    - Garden Club of Virginia Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Garden Club of Virginia Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Garden Club of Virginia Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Garden Club of Virginia Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Garden Club of Virginia Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Garden Club of Virginia Dedication Programs, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Garden Club of Virginia Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Garden Club of Virginia, Rolfe-Warren Plantation, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Mellon-Scaife Botanical Garden, 1966-1967; 5.
    The restoration of the main garden in Mellon Park is found in the Pittsburgh Point Breeze neighborhood. This garden was developed as a memorial to Mrs. Sarah Mellon Scaife. To memorialize Mrs. Scaife, Griswold designed, developed, and participated in the rededication of an outdoor botanical garden. The botanical garden was developed to serve not only as a memorial, but as a source of study for botanical students, landscape professionals, and amateur gardeners alike. This garden promoted both the scientific and aesthetic understanding required to create botanical gardens. Griswold worked on this project from 1966 to 1969.
    - Mellon-Scaife Botanical Garden, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - General Projects, 1924-1976; 6.
    The subseries contains material relating to Griswold's architectural landscape projects and his professional life. Some of these files contain documentary photographs, correspondence, and both architectural and business plans. Griswold worked on many residential and public landscape projects. Projects in this subseries are arranged in chronological and title order. Material in this subseries date from 1924 through 1976
    - Landscape Architecture Bibliographies, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Christmas Cards, Programs, and Invitations, 1924-1952 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Magazine Article Draft, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - J.W. Lawrence Contracts, Bids, and Speculations, 1928-1930 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - J.W. Lawrence Plans, 1929-1931 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
    - J.W. Lawrence Correspondence, 1929-1931 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - J.W. Lawrence Estimates and Computations, 1929-1931 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - J.W. Lawrence Bills, Acknowledgements, and Plant Materials, 1929-1931 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Physicians' Building, 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Physicians' Building, 1929-1931 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - J.J. Thompson: Estimates and Computations, 1929-1931 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - J.J. Thompson: Orders, Acknowledgements, and Bills, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - J.J. Thompson: Plant Lists, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - J.J. Thompson: Contact, Bids, Specifications, 1930-1931 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - J.J. Thompson: Correspondence, 1930-1933 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Fox Chapel Golf Club, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - West Virginia University, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - John B. Semple, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - John B. Semple, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - John B. Semple, 1931-1932 (Box 20, Folder 12-14)
    - R.F. Moreland: Contacts, Bids, Speculations, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - R.F. Moreland: Statement, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - R.F. Moreland: Plan, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - R.F. Moreland: Correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Falk Clinic, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Falk Clinic, 1930-1933 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Frank Semple, Jr., 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Sewickley Memorial, 1930-1933 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Twentieth Century Club, 1930-1933 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Rolling Rock Farms Plant Orders, Bills, and Receipts, 1930-1932 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
    - Rolling Rock Farms Work Summaries, Planting Lists, and Planting Records, 1930-1933 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Rolling Rock Club, 1930-1932 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania College for Women, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania College for Women, 1931-1932 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
    - Pennsylvania College for Women, 1931-1934 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania College for Women, Athletic Field, 1931-1951 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Howard K. Walter, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. R.J. Magee, 1931-1932 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Frank Semple: Correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Frank Semple: Estimates, Computations and Blueprint, 1931-1933 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - John M. Rice Consultation Receipt, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Robert Woods Bliss Blueprint, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Dr. F. Sonneborn and W. H. Daugherty, Sr., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - George Flinn, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - S.B. Linhart, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Mrs. A. Rex Flinn, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Garden Dictionary Entries, 1933-1934 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Garden Dictionary Entries, 1934-1935 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - W. J. Sloane Exhibition Garden, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Parks Association Correspondence, 1933-1940 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Chatham Village News, 1934-1939 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Rosenwald: Kraeger, Tree Inventory, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Rosenwald: Kraeger, Approved Bills, 1937-1939 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Rosenwald: Grunsfeld, 1937-1939 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Rosenwald: Kraeger, 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Rosenwald: Sprinkler System, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Rosenwald: Professional Service Agreements, 1938-1940 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Rosenwald: Cornell, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
    - Rosenwald: Fleisher, 1938-1940 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Rosenwald: Leopold, 1938-1940 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Rosenwald: Calculations, 1938-1940 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Rosenwald: Professional Statement, 1938-1942 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Lilian von Bonin, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - W.L. Mellon, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Charles J. Rosenbloom, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - W.L. Standish, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Singleton Paul, 1938-1940 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - J.D. Berg, 1938-1940 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - City of Pittsburgh Correspondence, 1938-1945 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Charles M. Stotz, 1938-1948 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Howard Walters, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Andover Terrace Building Project, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 10-11)
    - Alfred K. Stern, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 12-15)
    - H.C. McEldowney, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Joe Speidel, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - George R. Gibbons, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Nelson Wagner, 1939-1941 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Windsor and Hartsgrove Properties, 1939-1942 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Humphrey Morris: Presbyterian and Womens' Hospital, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Frederick Faris and Neil Stifel, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - C.F. Du Puy, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - David M. Levy, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Defense Housing: Clairton, Morgantown, Shaler, and Moon Townships, 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - William M. Robinson, 1941-1946 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Housing Authority Reports, 1943-1945 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - J.S. Lanahan, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Point Breeze Park Plans and Correspondence, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - American Commission for Living War Memorials, 1944-1945 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - American Commission for Living War Memorials, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Drake Park, 1944-1947 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Resignation from City Parks, Baltimore City Service Exam, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. John Frazer, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania State Parks, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 4-7)
    - Bellevue Park Abandoned Site, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Lockhart, Statement, and Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Kay Boys Club, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Babcock-Lott Enterprises, 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Veterans' Hospital Open Air Theater and Band Stand, 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Plate Glass, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny Conference Recreation Report, 1948-1950 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Zoological Society Correspondence, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Drake Well Park and Titusville Garden Club, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - James A. Bell and Westminster Place, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - John C. Conte: Valmar Garden, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Employee Applications, 1950-1955 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - R.F. Moreland, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Printing Orders, Griswold and Renner Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Charles Morgan Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Calvin Wells, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Ben Fairless, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Ward M. Canady Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Stuart Thompson Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Peat Moss Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Requests for Publication, Photographs of Pittsburgh, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Speaking Engagement Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Henry Ford II Estate, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
    - Leland Hazard, 1956-1957 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Pennsbury Manor Articles, Plans, Correspondence, and Landscape Study, 1957-1970 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Pennsbury Manor Plot Plan and General Information, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Pennsbury Manor Estimates and Contracts, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Dumbarton Oaks, 1959-1967 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
    - Kaufmann's Mount Lebanon Landscape Studies, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Williamsburg Symposium, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Antiques Forum Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Williamsburg: An Eighteenth-Century Garden City, Draft, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
    - Williamsburg: An Eighteenth-Century Garden City, Second Draft, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
    - Work Portfolio, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny Country Club Plans, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Westover Garden Rehabilitation Proposal and Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Allegheny Park Common Grounds Plan, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Thomas Robinson Memorial Gate, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Point State Park Correspondence, Photographs, and News Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Point State Park Correspondence and Photographs, 1969-1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Dormant Projects, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Robert E. Lee Foundation, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Gunston Hall Correspondence and Photographs, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Leslie Cheek Jr. Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Leslie Cheek Jr. Finances and Sketches, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Leslie Cheek Jr. Specs and Bids, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Leslie Cheek Jr. Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Neill Log House Restoration Correspondence and Photographs, 1968-1971 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - University of Virginia, 1968-1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Carll Tucker Jr. Tree Replacement, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Rock Ford, 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Stone Mountain, 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 5-7)
    - Winfred T. Grenfel, 1970-1973 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial, 1972-1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Caleb Pusey House Correspondence and Photographs, 1972-1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - George M. Modlin, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Prince George Street, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Blandford Cemetery, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Leland Hazard Peppercorn, 1973-1975 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Richmond Capital Grounds, 1973-1975 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Hugh Patterson, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Joseph Sellinger, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Mrs. Lothrop Reed, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - St. Thomas Church in Orange, Virginia, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - American Horticultural Society: Riverview Farm, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Robert A. Bristow, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Woodrow Wilson Birthplace, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Kenmore, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - N. David Kjellstrom, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Farnham Church, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Wildflower Refuge at the College of William and Mary, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Frick Fiasco, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Whittle House, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Media Material, undated; VI.
  Griswold used an abundance of media material in his research, planning, and eventually to highlight his completed landscapes. Griswold collected this material throughout his career both at home and abroad. There is evidence that some of the slides were used for conferences and educational lectures given by Griswold. This series contains sketches, architectural drawings and prints, postcards, photographs, 35mm slides, and negatives collected by Griswold. The photographs and negatives are presumed to be taken by Griswold and arranged using his original decimal system order. The images correspond to lectures, projects, conferences, and general reference of landscape architecture elements. Many of the images document Griswold's own completed landscape projects throughout his career. The print and photographic materials (Boxes 34-46) are now located in the media storage room for preservation purposes. Additional files relating to this material may be found in Series V.
  - Photographs, undated; 1.
    The photographs in this series are organized in Griswold's original decimal order from .000 to .121, and not all numbers are present in the collection. The photos initially had corresponding nitrate negatives affixed to the back of prints; the majority of the photos are undated. Additional files relating to this material may be found in Series V.
    - .000 Rome (Box 34)
    - .001 V. Abamalek
    - .002 V. Albani
    - .004 V. Aurelia
    - .005 V. Borghese
    - .006 Bosco Parrasio
    - .007 V. Chigi
    - .008 V. Colonna
    - .009 V. Corsini
    - .010 V. Doria Pamphily
    - .011 V. Madama
    - .012 V. Medici
    - .013 V. Papa Giulio
    - .014 V. Sciarra
    - .015 Viterbo
    - .016 V. Caprarola
    - .017 Soriano
    - .018 V. Lante
    - .020 V. Mondragone
    - .023 V. Torlonia
    - .024 V. Aldo Brandini
    - .025 V. Lanceolotti
    - .026 Castel Gondolfo
    - .027 Papal Palace
    - .028 V. Barberini
    - .030 V. Adriano
    - .031 V. D'Este
    - .032 Florence
    - .033 V. Palmieri
    - .034 V. Salviati
    - .035 V. Belriposo
    - .036 V. Medici
    - .037 V. Stibbert (Box 35)
    - .038 V. Gamberaia
    - .039 V. Corsi-Salviati
    - .040 V. Corsini
    - .042 V. Reale di Petra-ja
    - .043 V. Quarto
    - .044 V. La Pietra
    - .045 V. Poggia Imperiali
    - .046 V. Campi (Signa)
    - .047 V Colazzi
    - .048 Pal. Riccardi
    - .050 Boboli Gardens
    - .051 Sienna Gen'l
    - .052 V. Cetinale
    - .053 V. Segardi
    - .054 V. Chelsa
    - .055 V. Vicobella
    - .056 Lucca
    - .057 V. Torrigiana
    - .058 V. Bernardini
    - .059 V. Marlia
    - .060 V. Mansi
    - .061 V. Varcello
    - .063 V. Collodi
    - .064 Bologna Gen'l
    - .065 Parma Gen'l
    - .066 Padua
    - .067 Genoa
    - .068 Pal Doria
    - .069 V. Scassi
    - .071 V. Cicogna
    - .072 Varese
    - .073 Public Gardens, Genoa
    - .074 Lago Maggiore
    - .075 Isola Bella
    - .076 Como (Box 36)
    - .077 V. Crespi
    - .078 V. D'Este Como
    - .079 V. Carlotta
    - .080 V. Balbianello
    - .081 Pal Giovio
    - .082 Bellagio
    - .083 Venice
    - .084 Palladio Rotunda
    - .085 V. Valmarana
    - .086 Pal Dalla Ore Quirini
    - .087 Verona
    - .088 V. Cuzzano
    - .089 Stra-Brenta Canal
    - .090 Naples
    - .092 V. Caserta
    - .093 Roman Campagnia
    - .094 V. Borghese
    - .094S V. Opposite Borghese
    - .095 V. Passerini
    - .096 V. Giacomelli
    - .097 AM Academy
    - .098 Tabularium
    - .099 Campidoglio
    - .100 Miscellaneous
    - .101 Palermo
    - .102 Taormina
    - .103 Pal. Barberini
    - .104 V. Doria Dalle Rose
    - .105 V. Pliana
    - .106 Certosa di Pavia
    - .107 Arrezzo
    - .108 San Gimingnano
    - .109 Bergamo
    - .110 Volterra
    - .111 Segesta
    - .112 Pensione Cervieri Como
    - .113 Perugia Gen'l
    - .114 Vatican Garden
    - .115 Knights of Malta
    - .117 V. Catena
    - .118 Urbino Gen'l
    - .119 Ravenna
    - .119 V. Gori
    - .120 Pistoia Gen'l
    - .121 Prato Gen'l
    - Mounted landscape photographs
    - V. Aurelia (Box 37)
    - V. Sciara
    - Academy in Rome
    - Graniculum Park
    - State Park
    - State Park 35 mm Negatives
    - Mandel Photographs
    - Edison Dick Photographs
    - WL Mellon Photographs
    - Rosenwald Photographs
    - Cyrus McCormick Photographs
    - Ascoli Photographs
    - Burgettstown Swimming Pool Photographs
    - Lake Forest Flower Show
    - St. L Coal towns photographs
    - Miscellaneous England Photographs
    - Greece Photographs
    - 230 BD Phillips
    - 233 JE Lewis
    - 237 JW Lawrence
    - 253 HB Higgins
    - 254 FC Schroederer
    - 256 CH Mathews, Jr.
    - 275 Frank Semple
    - 279 Roy A Hunt
    - 286 JG Frazier
    - 291 Rolling Rock Club
    - 350 JM Schoonmaker
    - 506 Fox Chapel Club
    - 510 Mrs. Simon Patterson
    - 520 Calvin Wells
    - 535 Cyrus McCormick
    - 536 Buhl Foundation
    - 538 Edison Dick
    - 539 RE Clemson
    - 541 Robert Mandel
    - Mrs. Adler
    - Mrs. Walter Brewster
    - J & L Steel
    - Miscellaneous postcards
    - Monticello postcards, 1925
    - Mount Vernon Ladies Association postcards
  - Negatives, undated; 2.
    The negatives in this series are organized in Griswold's original decimal order from .000 to .121 and the correspond to the prints in the Photographs Subseries; these are then followed by miscellaneous unidentified negatives. The Corresponding print negatives are 3x5 nitrate negatives that were originally affixed to the back of prints and are located in Boxes 38 and 39. Box 40 contains 8x10 glass plate negatives of models of Caprarolo, Griswold workspace, and plan of Cicogna. Additional files relating to this project may be found in Series V. The majority of these negatives are undated.
    - Rome .000 to.121Prato Gent'l (corresponding photo negatives) (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous unnumbered collections negatives
    - Rome-Villa Aurelia, Villa Sciara, Academy in Rome, Graniculum Park
    - Mandel
    - Montacute
    - Edison Dick
    - State Park
    - W.L. Mellon
    - Rosenwald
    - Cyrus McCormick
    - Ascoli
    - Burgettstown swimming pool
    - Compton Wingate
    - Canons Ashby
    - St. L Vestaburg
    - Lake Forest Flower Show
    - St. L Coal towns
    - Miscellaneous English
    - Miscellaneous Unidentified
    - Academia Americana, 6 glass plate negatives, 5 unidentified, undated
    - Tram with Driver and Promotional Banner, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915 (Box 39)
    - Street with People, Tram, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Palace Of Machinery, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Palace Of Education, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Palace Of Education, Full View, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Fountain, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - California State Building, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Palm Lined Path, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Kiosk, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Structure Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Corinthian Column Structure, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Corinthian Column Structure, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Corinthian Column Arcade with Many People (Palace Of Fine Arts) Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Large Building and Plaza with People
    - Corinthian Columns and Figure
    - Corinthian Column Structure (Palace Of Fine Arts) Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Garden with Male in Background
    - Fountain, Statue and Building
    - Corinthian Column Arcade with Many People (Palace Of Fine Arts) Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition 1915, undated
    - Unidentified Tower
    - Road, Tower, Rotunda, and Arch
    - Large Structure with Automobiles, Panama Pacific Int'l Exhibition, 1915
    - Arches with People
    - Fountain with Statues
    - Topiary Being Exploited for Group Photograph
    - Path through Foliage with Illustrated Detail
    - Geologically Unique Landscape with Horses
    - Garden with Topiary
    - Mountainous, Forested Landscape
    - Landscape with House
    - Courtyard
    - Road Leading to Gate
    - Italian Fountain with Statues
    - Forest with Tipi
    - Garden
    - Landscape
    - Courtyard and Veranda
    - Circular Fountain
    - Fountain
    - Fountain
    - Landscape
    - Landscape with Field, Buildings, and Hills
    - Forest Landscape
    - Lake
    - Hedge Lined Row with Human in Background
    - Rocky Landscape with Waterfall
    - Forest Landscape with Path
    - Path to House with Male Figure
    - Mountain Landscape
    - Stone Edifice with Female and Animal in Foreground
    - Marsh with Waterfowl
    - Path
    - Arbor
    - Terrace with Male Figure
    - Garden
    - 230 B.D.Phillips
    - 237J.W. Lawrence
    - 253 H.B. Higgins
    - 256 C.H. Mathews, Jr.
    - 275 Frank Semple
    - 279 Roy A. Hunt
    - 286 J.G. Frazier
    - 29 Rolling Rock Club
    - 350 J.M. Schoonmaker
    - Fox Chapel Club 500
    - 510 Mrs. Simon Patterson
    - 520 Calvin Wells
    - 535 Cyrus McCormick
    - 536 Suhl Foundation
    - 538 Dick Edison
    - 539 R. E.Clemson
    - 541 Robert Mandel
    - Mrs. Adler
    - Mrs. WaltersBrewster
    - Miscellaneous negatives
    - Model of Caprarolo 1, undated (Box 40)
    - Model of Caprarolo 2, undated
    - Model of Caprarolo 3, undated
    - Mozzoni Cicogna, undated
    - Griswold Workspace 1, undated
    - Griswold Workspace 2, undated
    - Plan of Cicogna 1, undated
    - Plan of Cicogna 2, undated
  - Slides, undated; 3.